I'll wipe out all the Fieldsauruses!
我会把菲尔多龙全部歼灭的
The town
这个城镇
has undergone tremendous changes.
发生了巨大的变化
All the materials are mine!
素材都是我的哦
I have to deal with the disputes again.
又得去调解纷争了
Yo, Rud.
嗨 路德
That's a troubled face you have there.
你的脸色很不好哦
Bu. Gali.
步 加利
You just became the leader of a clan.
你才刚成为战团的团长
I suppose this is a bit much on your shoulders.
这个状况确实让人吃不消呢
Maybe you should let someone else handle things?
是不是应该交给你以外的人 来控管啊
Yes, about that,
是啊 关于这部分
I have a favour to ask of you.
我有些事想拜托你们
Welcome back.
欢迎回来
Oh. Another dispute?
呃 又起纷争了吗
Yes.
是啊
Well, Fieldsauruses are perfect for making potions and weapons,
毕竟菲尔多龙是个很适合 用来做药水和武器的素材啊
so it's no surprise everyone's keen to take them down.
难怪大家都抢着要讨伐它
I guess you do need some help
想经营一个战团
to run a clan.
果然必须找人过来帮忙呢
Yes.
对啊
Manicia's handling the day-to-day stuff,
庶务工作目前交给玛妮西娅负责
but we can't let her be too overworked.
但又不能让她太操劳
I asked Lilia, but…
虽然我也有问过莉莉亚…
Sorry.
抱歉
My information bank isn't enough to guide you through this.
我拥有的知识 也没有专业到可以指导你们
Maybe you should ask the other clans.
不如拜托其他战团帮忙吧
The other clans, huh?
帮忙…吗
Though, the ideal situation
不过最理想的状况
would be to form an alliance with other clans.
还是能结盟什么的
That way, you'll be on equal standing.
这样你们之间就是对等的同盟关系
If you end up under another clan,
如果附属在其他战团底下
it'd defeat the whole purpose of establishing a clan in the first place.
就会失去在镇上 新建一个战团的意义
ALLIANCE A CLAN LEADER, B CLAN LEADER
(同盟的情况 (A战团团长 B站团团长)
But if you want to ally with another clan,
只是 想跟其他战团结为同盟的话
it might be challenging if you don't have something to bring to the table.
如果对方没能从中捞点好处 或许很难达成共识
Our clan only has Nin, Luna,
毕竟我们战团只有妮恩 露娜
Manicia, and me, after all.
以及玛妮西娅和我而已
If only you had something you could show them right away.
如果你们有可以马上 展现给对方看的东西就好了
Lily.
莉莉
Something we can show the others right now, huh?
我们现在可以 展现给对方看的东西啊
Only our combat strength, I think.
也就只有战力了吧
However,
不过
doing so might reveal that we're protecting Marius.
这样会被别人发现 我们有意包庇玛里乌斯
So, we can only tell them we've repelled the guardian.
所以只能告诉对方 我们击退了守护者而已
You have a point.
说得也是
Seems like
这么看来
we really need someone to guide us on how to manage a clan.
果然还是需要找人 来指导我们怎么经营战团吧
But after listening to Lilia's advice,
不过听完莉莉亚的建议
I've been doing my best to put in the effort.
我也尽自己所能地努力过了
You truly live up to being a clan leader.
不愧是战团团长
How dependable.
真可靠呢
At this rate,
这样下去
we might just end up becoming a large clan soon.
搞不好意外地 马上就能变成大型战团咯
You don't sound too happy about that.
为什么你的语气听起来 似乎觉得有些可惜啊
Well, if that happens,
因为 那样的话
we won't get
可以像这样
to spend as much time alone together anymore.
两人独处的时间就会减少了吧
Rud.
路德
If you can't find any allies of helpers,
如果你找不到合作伙伴或人手
you can use my identity for publicity.
也可以拿我的事去宣传哦
I can't do that.
这我办不到
You dislike that.
你不是讨厌那样吗
Rud, you really are…
路德 你真的是…
Rud, become the manager of the labyrinth!
路德 来当迷宫的管理者吧
What are you doing?
你们在干嘛
Nothing.
没干嘛
Didn't I already refuse?
那件事我不是拒绝过了吗
I'm quite busy now.
我现在可是很忙的
Then I'll join your clan
那我也加入你的战团
and help you stop the fights.
帮你阻止大家吵架吧
That's not all you do in a clan.
战团又不是只要做那个就好
By the way,
话说回来
is it all right for the guardian to be wandering around like this?
守护者可以这样随意走动吗
Not a problem at all.
没问题
Then,
那么
do you harbour any…
你对人类没有什么…
resentment towards humans?
怨恨之类的吗
Are you really asking that?
你真的要问这个吗
So, he does.
果然有
Looks like he has a story to tell.
看来之前发生过什么事呢
Not even the slightest.
一点怨恨都没有
So, let me help you.
所以 让我帮忙吧
And, in turn, you help me manage the labyrinth.
然后 拜托你帮我管理迷宫吧
Fine.
知道了啦
I'll let you join the clan.
我允许你加入我们
Explain the labyrinth management again.
然后再跟我说明一次 管理迷宫的事吧
Let's get going then.
那就赶紧出发吧
I haven't agreed to become the manager, though.
我还没答应要成为管理者哦
THE STRONGEST TANK'S LABYRINTH RAIDS
《最强肉盾的迷宫攻略～拥有稀少技能体力9999的肉盾，被勇者队伍辞退了》
Rud, come.
路德 过来这里
Do you usually manage the labyrinth from here?
你平时就是在这里管理迷宫吗
That's right.
没错
This pool reflects the internal conditions of the labyrinth.
这个池子会倒映出迷宫内部的状况
You also adjust the monster configuration and labyrinth structure here.
也可以从这边调整魔物的配置 和迷宫构造
See the points?
这里不是有点数吗
You can create or replicate monsters
只要使用点数
just by using points.
就可以制造或复制魔物
Do these points automatically increase?
这个点数会自动增加吗
Points increase over time
随着时间流逝 或是削掉冒险者的护盾
or by depleting an adventurer's shield force.
就能回收点数
I see.
原来如此
So, for example,
举例来说
if you deplete an amount of my shield force,
只要你从我身上削掉大量的护盾
you can recover an equivalent amount of points?
就能回收同等的点数吗
Oh, you can do that?
原来还有这一招吗
Can you demonstrate it to me?
可以实际操作一次给我看吗
Sure.
好啊
Are you cloning a Goblin?
你要复制哥布林吗
I'm summoning it into the labyrinth.
是要召唤到迷宫里哦
-Hey, that will scare off the adventurers. -Ow…
-喂 这样冒险者会死掉的 -好痛…
Can you clone other monsters besides Goblins?
哥布林以外的魔物也可以复制吗
Yes.
可以
The only ones we can currently clone are…
不过现在可以复制的魔物只有…
Goblins,
哥布林
Axe Orcs,
战斧半兽人
Chameleon Kongs,
变色龙金刚
and Fieldsauruses.
菲尔多龙 这四种
Only monsters created through "Creation" can be cloned.
因为只有那些透过"制造"获得的 自创魔物才可以复制
By the way,
顺带一提
if you can establish a trust relationship with a monster,
如果你能跟魔物建立信赖关系
they might help you in dire situations
在紧要关头 他们还会帮助你
and even become quite fond of you.
也有可能变得很亲近你哦
Will monsters really bond with humans?
魔物真的会亲近人类吗
It costs a million points?
是说 居然要花费100万点
It's impossible to create new monsters.
这根本不可能制造嘛
That's right.
没错
That's where the grimoire comes in.
这时候就要使用这本魔导书
It's an item that can let you randomly create monsters.
这是一个可以随机制造魔物的道具
It's like a lottery.
简单来说就像抽奖
Want to try it?
要试试看吗
APPEARS
(跳出)
Slime?
史莱姆？
It's a little different from what I explained,
虽然跟刚才说的状况有些不同
but it grew attached to you quite quickly.
但他一下子就变得很亲近你呢
Does this mean we can create Slimes now?
这样以后就能复制史莱姆了吗
Correct.
没错
That means
如此一来
with time,
只要花一点时间
we may be able to create S-rank monsters.
或许就能制造出S位阶的魔物了呢
Adventurers to Avancier
来阿凡锡亚的冒险者
mostly come for the Fieldsauruses.
多半是为了菲尔多龙而来的
While they're popular now,
虽然现在很受欢迎
the flow of people will likely decrease
但是等市面上到处都看得到素材后
once their drop is readily available everywhere.
人流肯定会减少
If I become one of the managers,
如果成为管理者
I can add various types of monsters into the labyrinth
或许就在迷宫里 添加各种各样的魔物
to stabilise the flow of adventurers.
借此稳定冒险者的流量
This…
这个…
could also be applied to managing the clan.
应该也能运用在经营战团上
The hit just now recovered 1000 points.
刚才那一击可以回收1000点
Hey, Rud!
喂 路德
I think that little guy's a Rare Slime!
这家伙好像是稀有史莱姆
Creating such a powerful creature. You really struck gold!
居然制造出这么厉害的家伙 你真是赚到了啊
Thank you, Slime.
谢谢你 史莱姆
Thanks to you, I've got a great idea.
多亏有你 我想到了一个好主意哦
Marius,
玛里乌斯
I'll manage the labyrinth in your stead.
我就代替你管理迷宫吧
Really?
真的吗
Not right away.
虽然不是马上就能帮忙
But I'll think carefully about what kind of labyrinth I want to create
但我会先想好 要打造出怎样的迷宫
to attract adventurers.
才能吸引冒险者过来
Can I trouble you to manage it for a while longer?
所以可以麻烦你再管理一段时间吗
I'll accept that.
好吧 我接受这个条件
What should we do about this little guy?
那…那这家伙该怎么办才好
It doesn't like me at all.
毕竟他根本不靠近我
You should take it with you.
不如你就带回家吧
Slime?
史莱姆
It's okay, Luna.
露娜 你别紧张
Well, um, I ended up with this little thing somehow.
不是 那个 这家伙算是我意外捡到
And Manicia's always wanted a pet…
而且玛妮西娅以前 也说过想要养宠物
It looks cuter than the other Slimes out there.
总觉得它好像 比外面的史莱姆来得可爱耶
Aw, so cute.
好可爱哦
Big Brother,
哥哥
if we're keeping it,
如果要把这孩子当宠物养
we should give it a name.
那就必须给它取个名字吧
You're right.
也是
Master,
主人
you came up with my name almost immediately.
您之前不是很快 就帮我取好名字了吗
You didn't…
当时该不会…
just pick a name, did you?
是随便取的吧
No, I didn't!
才…才没有呢
I thought it over
我可是经过深思熟虑
and came up with a cute name.
特地取了一个可爱的名字哦
I think you said it was because
我记得哥哥好像说
a Lunafia petal fell on Miss Luna.
是因为露娜小姐的衣服上 有一片露娜菲亚的花瓣吧？
That was surprisingly spontaneous of you.
没想到哥哥意外地随便呢
R… Right.
对…对了
How do you feel about the name "Lime"?
你觉得"莱伊姆" 这个名字怎么样
I think it likes it.
看来它似乎很喜欢呢
That's great.
太好了
Nice to meet you, Lime.
请多指教咯 莱伊姆
I love seeing you flustered.
我最喜欢看哥哥困扰的表情了
Me too.
我也是
Give me a break…
饶了我吧
Avancier's clan leader?
阿凡锡亚的战团团长
Why would we form an alliance with a clan from such a rural town?
我们为何要跟那种 乡下小镇的战团结盟
Bu, reject them.
步 去拒绝他
No, wait.
不 等等
This kid seems interesting.
这孩子还挺有趣的嘛
Very well.
好吧
In a few days, the two major clans will be holding a ball.
过几天有一场两大战团合办的舞会
-Invite them. -Invite them to join us.
-去邀请他过来 -邀他一起来参加吧
Days later,
后来又过了几天
we found ourselves in Caird.
我们现在在凯路德镇
This town's bigger than I imagined.
这个城镇比我想象中还大呢
Lilia, Lily,
莉莉亚 莉莉
thank you for coming along.
谢谢你们陪我们来
Don't mention it.
不用客气
We can stop by the guild here too.
反正我们也能顺便 跟这边的公会打个招呼
It's my first time attending a ball.
我还是第一次参加舞会
How exciting, Lilia.
真令人期待呢 姐姐
Rud, what does that flag represent?
路德 那个旗子是什么
It's the same pattern as the one printed here.
就跟这上面印得图案一样
Those are the flags of Black Dragon Fang and White Tiger Claw.
那些是象征着"黑龙之牙" 以及"白虎之爪"的旗子
Those flags are everywhere.
两团的旗子都挂得满满的呢
Everyone's here, yes?
所有人都到了吧
Take a look at this.
你们看这个
It's the invitation to a ball
这是"黑龙之牙"和"白虎之爪"…
from the two major clans of Caird, Black Dragon Fang and White Tiger Claw.
也就是凯路德的 两大战团寄来的舞会邀请函
Isn't it great that you got an invitation, Big Brother?
能收到邀请函 不是很厉害的事吗 哥哥
Though I'm not entirely clear,
虽然不是很清楚
Master is indeed quite formidable.
但主人果然很强呢
Look.
我说啊
I doubt they're interested in being chummy.
他们肯定不是想跟我们 一起友好地经营战团吧
What conditions did they propose?
作为回报 他们提了什么条件？
You're right.
你说的没错
They rejected the alliance proposal.
结盟一事已经被他们拒绝了
However, they said they might consider letting us become their subsidiary.
不过他们说可以考虑 让我们归属于他们之下
I knew it.
果然是这样
That's not all.
但问题不只如此
In return for their help,
作为帮忙的交换条件
they want Nin.
他们想跟我们索取妮恩
Nin?
索取妮恩？
Nin is a renowned saint.
妮恩作为圣女非常有名
It's not just the two clans. Others have brought it up before as well.
其实不光是两大战团 也有其他人跟我提过这件事
But most of them came for Nin.
但大部分的人都是冲着妮恩来的
I'm in high demand, after all.
毕竟我很抢手啊
So, what are you going to do?
所以 你打算怎么做？
Are you going to hand me over?
要把我…交出去吗？
If you want to go, I won't stop you.
如果你想去的话 我不会阻止你
What if I ask you not to give me up, no matter what?
那如果我拜托你 无论如何都不要把我交出去呢
Then I'll turn them down.
那我就会拒绝他们
Then reject them.
那就拒绝吧
I don't plan on affiliating myself with any other clan.
我可不打算归属于其他战团哦
I understand.
我知道了
I'll turn them down no matter what.
无论发生什么事 我都会拒绝他们的
But
不过
I am prepared to attend the ball,
我打算抱持着参加鸿门宴的觉悟
knowing the lurking dangers.
去参加舞会
The guests will likely belong
我想舞会的来宾
to either Black Dragon Fang or White Tiger Claw.
应该都是黑龙之牙或白虎之爪的人
I cannot pass up this opportunity
但我不能放过这个
to speak directly to the leaders of the two major clans.
能直接跟两大战团的 代表人对话的机会
You're right.
说得也是
Now is not the time to retreat. It's time to take the initiative.
这个时候不该退缩 而是应该主动进攻呢
Caird…
凯路德…
What's wrong?
怎么了吗
Nothing, just remembered something unimportant.
没什么 只是想起一件不重要的事
I once saw a labyrinth
我曾在那个池子里 看过一个和我一样
with a sentient guardian just like me in that pond.
"守护者拥有自我意识"的迷宫
And the labyrinth's name is the same as the town called Caird,
而那个迷宫的名字 跟那个叫凯路德的城镇相同
"Caird Labyrinth."
叫做"凯路德迷宫"
That's important information!
这很重要好吗
Is that so?
很重要吗？
In other words,
也就是说
if we can conquer Caird Labyrinth
只要攻略"凯路德迷宫"
and obtain another magic stone,
再拿到一颗魔石的话
perhaps Manicia's illness can be completely cured.
或许就能完全治好玛妮西娅的病了
Caird Labyrinth.
凯路德迷宫
I heard that the two major clans
听说那两大战团
only ever managed to break through to the 50th floor.
似乎也只能突破到第50层
But we've grown a lot during this time.
但是我们这阵子成长了很多
Not only do we have Marius with impeccable fire power,
不仅有火力强到无可挑剔的 玛里乌斯
but also Luna, who practices magic whenever she has free time,
还有只要有空就会练习魔法的露娜
and the excellent healer Nin.
以及优秀的补师 妮恩
I think we should be able to form a great party.
我认为我们应该 可以组成一支很棒的队伍
Raid the labyrinth and find an alliance.
不仅要攻略迷宫 还要找战团结盟
It looks like we're going to have a very interesting trip.
看来这次的旅行会很有趣呢
I'm sure neither will be easy to achieve.
不论是哪一边 肯定都不容易达成
But I must form an alliance with them
但我一定要和他们结盟
and obtain the labyrinth treasure.
还要拿到迷宫秘宝
Sorry to keep you waiting.
让你们久等了
Well? Doesn't it suit me?
怎么样 很适合吧
It does.
是啊
I did try to get Luna to wear a dress like me.
我是有建议露娜跟我一起穿礼服啦
I… I think I look better in this.
我…我觉得自己比较适合穿这件
You'd look beautiful in a dress, too,
虽然你穿礼服应该也很好看
but the maid outfit suits you.
但女仆装也很适合你哦
Thank... Thank you.
谢…谢谢您
Lilia, you need to walk with your head held high.
姐姐真是的 走路要抬头挺胸才行
These girly clothes
我不是很喜欢这种…
are really not for me.
女孩子气的衣服
Don't worry, you look adorable.
放心啦 姐姐很可爱哦
Don't keep staring at me.
不要一直看我这边
Lilia is shy.
莉莉亚害羞了
Stop that.
就说了 不要这样啦
This is a fancy ball.
这个舞会好豪华哦
This all belongs to Black Dragon Fang, after all.
毕竟这些全都是黑龙之牙的东西啊
It really opens your eye.
真的很惊人呢
I heard White Tiger Claw has similar establishments.
听说白虎之爪也有类似的房子哦
Truly the clans that rule above others, huh?
不愧是君临于 所有人之上的战团…吗
Isn't that Saint Nin?
那不是圣女大人吗
It is her.
真的耶
Why is she attending our clan's ball?
为什么她会来我们战团的舞会？
Didn't you know?
你不知道吗
Rumour has it that Saint Nin's clan is becoming a subsidiary of ours.
听说圣女大人的战团 好像要归顺于我们战团哦
Where did that come from?
那又是什么谣言？
And they make it sound
而且
like Nin's the leader of our clan.
说得好像妮恩 才是我们战团的代表人
Leader,
团长
you can't let them look down on us.
你可不能这样任由他人小看哦
Show them what we're made of.
趁今天让大家对你改观吧
That was the plan.
我本来就打算妥善处理这个问题
I had prepared myself for this,
虽然早就做好心理准备了
but it is really uncomfortable here…
但这个空间果真让人很不舒服呢
Rud!
欸 路德
Can I eat the food over there?
那边的食物可以吃吗
Yes.
可…可以
Got it.
这样啊
Marius's really good at easing the tension.
只要有玛里乌斯在 就会变得没那么紧张呢
Yes, we should get some food too.
对啊 我们也去吃点东西吧
Thank you all for attending tonight's ball.
谢谢大家前来参加今天的舞会
I am Ike, the subleader of Black Dragon Fang.
我是黑龙之牙的副团长 艾克
I am Cynthia, the subleader of White Tiger Claw.
我是白虎之爪的副团长 辛西亚
I thought the leaders of both clans would be present.
我还以为两边都会 派代表人出来问候呢
We have invited a special guest.
今天我们邀请了一位 特别嘉宾来到现场
Saint Nin,
圣女大人
may we invite you to come on stage?
可以请您上台一下吗
Rud,
路德
those guys are calling me.
那些家伙好像在叫我上去
But I am Nin from your clan.
但我是你的战团里的妮恩
Yes.
是啊
I'll go and correct them.
我去跟他们抱怨几句
Can you come up with me?
你可以跟我一起上台吗
Saint Nin,
圣女大人
I didn't expect you to officially become an adventurer.
没想到您居然会正式成为冒险者
It's truly a surprise.
实在让我深感意外
Is that so?
是吗
I've always wanted to focus on being an adventurer.
我倒是从以前开始 就很想专心当个冒险者了
May I ask who the man next to you is?
那么 请问您身旁的男人是？
Who is that guy?
那家伙是谁啊
He's too close to the saint.
居然跟圣女大人装熟
He is…
他是…
Nice to meet you.
初次见面
I am Rud, the leader of the clan Nin belongs to.
我是妮恩所属的战团的团长 路德
Aren't you the man who used to be part of the hero's party?
你不是那个曾经隶属于 勇者小队的男人吗
I remember your class
我记得你的职业
was a tank, right?
好像是肉盾吧
The former hero even said you were useless.
前勇者不是还说你"派不上用场"吗
He consulted me
当时
on his party formation issues
针对队伍成员的编制问题
many times.
他来找我讨论过很多次
So I suggested he just kick out the tank.
所以我就建议他 "干脆把肉盾开除吧"
What?
什么
Raiding the labyrinth doesn't require a tank.
因为攻略迷宫不需要肉盾啊
You say it doesn't need a tank?
你说不需要…肉盾？
That's right.
是的
The tank is supposed to protect the party from attacks,
因为肉盾表面上 是在守护同伴不受攻击
but in reality, they serve no purpose.
但实际上根本没有在工作
Exactly.
就是说啊
-Attackers can -If you must have one,
-而且还能让攻击手顶替肉盾的工作 -真要选的话 也会选回避型肉盾
I will cut straight to the point. Saint Nin,
我就单刀直入地说了 妮恩大人
won't you join our clan?
您要不要加入我们战团呢
Staying in a no-name clan
待在这种默默无名的战团
will only hide your true potential.
是无法让您大放异彩的
Hold on!
等等
We need an excellent healer
为了攻略凯路德迷宫
to conquer the Caird Labyrinth too.
我们这里也想要优秀的补师啊
Enough.
别说了
I have no intention of handing over Nin.
我并不打算把妮恩交给你们
Mister Rud.
路德先生
Aren't you looking for a clan advisor?
你不是想要一个战团顾问吗
But you wanted Nin in exchange.
但你们不是希望我用妮恩来交换吗
I'm sorry, but Nin is an important ally.
虽然很抱歉 但妮恩是我重要的伙伴
I wouldn't trade her for anything.
我不会把她当作交换条件
So, why are you here?
那么 你为什么要来这里？
I want to form an alliance with you.
我想和你们结盟
An alliance?
结盟？
Is he suggesting an alliance with our clan?
他是想跟我们这个大战团结盟吗
Isn't he from some weak clan in the countryside?
他不是乡下的弱小战团吗
And he's just a tank.
而且还只是个肉盾
This has to be a joke.
他是在开玩笑吧
Just knowing a tank is the clan leader
光是让肉盾来当团长这一点
is unsettling.
就已经够让我不安了
Saint Nin,
妮恩大人
do you really want to be around a man like this?
您真的要待在这种男人身边吗
Yes, of course.
是啊 那当然
Because he's the strongest tank in the world!
因为他是世上最强的肉盾
May I borrow the mic?
可以借用一下麦克风吗
We came here to conquer Caird Labyrinth.
我们是为了攻略凯路德迷宫 才来这里的
We're better than everyone in this room.
我们比在场的所有人都还厉害
You can laugh all you want.
你们想笑就笑吧
But
不过
those who laugh now will regret it later.
现在笑的人之后一定会后悔的
We will surpass your expectations.
我们绝对会让你们的期待落空
We will conquer the Caird Labyrinth up to the 51st floor,
我们会将凯路德迷宫攻略到
a feat neither of the two major clans have achieved.
两大战团都无法突破的51层之上
We
我们
will achieve our goal.
绝对会达成目标的
That's a good spirited young man.
真是个有气势的年轻人啊
I like people like that.
我最喜欢这样的人了
Leader…
团…团长
You came.
原来您也来了吗
Yes.
是啊
Ike, I've told you not to underestimate newcomers.
艾克 就叫你不要太小看新人
That's a bad habit of yours.
你这一点真的很不好哦
But…
可是…
Rud, was it?
你叫做路德吧
I am Gothew, the leader of Black Dragon Fang.
我是黑龙之牙的团长 哥修
It's a pleasure to meet you.
请多指教
Just by shaking hands,
光靠握手就能知道
you can tell he's got extraordinary strength.
他拥有异于常人的强大力量
So this is the leader of Black Dragon Fang.
这就是黑龙之牙的团长吗
If this guy can conquer the labyrinth,
如果这家伙真的能攻略迷宫
then I'll consider an alliance with them.
那我也可以考虑跟你们结盟哦
Stop hiding and say something.
别躲了 你也说些什么吧
Goodness.
真是的
I was going to pretend I wasn't around.
我本来打算装不在蒙混过关的
Don't say that,
别这么说嘛
Miss Ryutel, the leader of White Tiger Claw.
白虎之爪的团长 卢特尔小姐
If this clan can conquer the labyrinth,
如果这个战团可以攻略迷宫的话
I might consider the possibility of an alliance.
我也可以稍微考虑一下结盟的事哦
The condition being that you first successfully conquer the labyrinth.
不过 前提是你们要成功攻略迷宫
That's what she said, Rud.
她是这么说的哦 路德
Show us you're not all bluff.
你可不要只是虚张声势哦
That was a great speech!
那个宣言真不错呢
Please let that go.
拜托你不要再说刚才的事了
By the way,
话说回来
why don't people know how strong you are?
大家为什么不知道你有多强啊
Because generally speaking, you can't tell with just the eyes.
因为一般来说 光用眼睛看是看不出什么的
No… anyone with a certain level of strength can tell.
不…凡是有一定力量的人 都看得出来吧
That you're not an ordinary person.
看得出你不是普通人
Rud, you must conquer the labyrinth.
路德 你一定要攻略迷宫哦
I don't like seeing you being treated as a joke.
因为我不喜欢 你一直被别人当成笑话
Well then, I'm off to take a bath.
那么 我去洗澡咯
Don't give anyone any trouble.
不要给别人添麻烦哦
I know.
我知道啦
Master.
主人
You look tired.
你看起来很累呢
It's not often I get to speak in front of so many people.
因为很少有机会 在那么多人面前讲话
But
不过
you were very impressive just now, Master.
主人刚才说的话很帅气哦
I was very happy to hear it.
我听了觉得很开心
Indeed.
是啊
And, well…
而且 那个…
Thank you
谢…谢谢你
for standing up for me.
当时那样护着我
That made me really happy.
真的让我很高兴
Of course.
这是一定要的
You're my important comrade.
因为你是我重要的伙伴啊
Anyway, I just wanted to thank you.
总…总而言之 我只是想跟你道个谢而已
See you tomorrow.
那就明天见咯
The labyrinth that even the two major clans couldn't conquer.
两大战团都无法攻略的迷宫
It won't be easy,
虽然知道这不是一件容易的事
but to protect my clan and friends,
但是为了守护战团和伙伴们
I must
我绝对
conquer Caird Labyrinth.
会成功攻略凯路德迷宫的